<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, MainActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">OpenWatch Recorder</string>
    <string name="record_video">Record Audio</string>
    <string name="record_audio">Record Video</string>
    <string name="recording_saved">Recording saved</string>
    <string name="upload_recording_now">Would you like to upload your recording now?</string>
    <string name="yes_upload">Yes, upload now!</string>
    <string name="no_quit">No, just quit please</string>
    <string name="uploading_file">Uploading file!</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="title_ex">The name of the event</string>
    <string name="pub">Public description</string>
    <string name="pub_ex">ex, footage of a private security officer assaulting a man at an airport, a judge taking a bribe</string>
    <string name="priv">Private description</string>
    <string name="priv_ex">Any notes you may which to tell the OW admins. Remove names, change voices, etc</string>
    <string name="upload">Upload!</string>
    <string name="please_describe">Please describe your recording!\n</string>
    <string name="location_on">Location: On</string>
    <string name="location_off">Location: Off</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="uploading">Uploading..</string>
    <string name="uploading_sub">This may take some time</string>
    <string name="upload_done">Upload finished!</string>
    <string name="open">Select File to Upload</string>
    <string name="tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="upload_or_play">Upload or Play?</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="about_text">OpenWatch is a participatory citizen media project aiming to provide documentary evidence of uses and abuses of power.\n\

				Until now, surveillance technology has only been in the hands of those who are already in power, which means it cannot be used to combat the largest problem facing modern society: abuse of power.\n\n
				So the question remains: Who watches the watchers? \n\n
				This is where OpenWatch comes in. Now, we are all opportunistic journalists. Whenever any of us come in contact with power being used or abused, we can capture it and make it become part of the public record. If we seek truth and justice, we will be able to appeal to documentary evidence, not just our word against theirs. Ideally, this will mean less corruption, more open government and a more transparent society.\n\n
				OpenWatch is not only intended to display abuse of power, but also to highlight appropriate use. As we are unbound by technological restrictions, we can aim to record every single time power is applied so that we may analyze global trends and provide a record for future historians.\n\n
				Police, corporate executives, judges, lawyers, private security agents, lobbyists, bankers, principals and politicians: be mindful! We are watching! \n\n\nOpenWatch is Free and Open Source Software. More information is available at OpenWatch.net\n\n\n</string>
    
    <string name="tutorial_text">Welcome, new Watcher!\n\n Whenever you think you are about to interact with an authority figure or a person in a position of power, start OpenWatch and either press Record Audio or Record Video. \n\nIf you record audio, the application will appear to close, although audio is still being recorded. When the encounter is over, reopen the application and it will stop the recording and prompt you for a description for the upload. For best audio quality, put the phone in your front shirt pocket, or on a nearby table with the microphone facing upwards.\n\n
    							 If you are recording video, the screen will simply turn black, as if the phone were off. To stop the recording, press the back button three times, which will then stop the recording and prompt you to upload. To avoid suspicion while filming, simply pretend to be making a phone call.\n\n
    							 When uploading, please describe the incident. It will be reviewed by the editors and quickly published to OpenWatch.net. If you request, we will remove all of the personally identifiable information we can. No logs are kept on the server.\n\nAll uploads are released under the Creative-Commons-Attribution license.\n\nCourage is contagious!\n\n\n</string>
    
    
	<string name="menu_new_folder">New Folder</string>
    <string name="menu_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="menu_rename">Rename</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="menu_open">Open</string>
    <string name="menu_move">Move</string>
    <string name="menu_copy">Copy</string>
    
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    
</resources>
